Kelechukwu Cos-Ibe

+447706529322 | chiderakelly@outlook.com Gateshead, Newcastle upon Tyne, NE8 4AB United Kingdom https://cosibe.github.io

Hello Team,

You are a great organisation with a dedicated team and you would be wondering why you should hire me for the role of a full stack web developer.

Here's why:

I have working experience and knowledge of HTML, CSS, JavaScript and MJML. Okay maybe that's not enough, everybody seems to have that these

I HAVE over 1 year of startup experience, so I know what it means to wear many hats, grow a business, sales and marketing, responding to user needs and market research while bootstrapping. Still not enough? Keep reading...

I will add to the diversity on your team and research has shown that diversity often makes for better, more successful teams.

If by now, I have given you a reason to consider my application and I really hope I have, then go through my resume attached.

I hope to hear from you soon.

Kelechukwu Cos-Ibe

Gateshead, Newcastle upon Tyne, NE8 4AB United Kingdom +447706529322 | chiderakelly@outlook.com https://cosibe.github.io

Objective

I seek challenging opportunities where I can fully use my skills for the success of the organization.

Experience

Central Employment United Kingdom

04-2021 - Present

Warehouse Operative

- Worked in Quality control department of a food factory
- Made sure food were processed perfectly
- Worked in a team of five people

Magnarex Technology, Nigeria

03-2019 - 09-2020

Email developer / Marketer

- Worked voluntarily to gain experience
- Worked in a team
- Designed and developed email for marketing
- Developed landing pages

Education

Northumbria University, Newcastle upon Tyne, United Kingdom.

01-2021 to Present

Computer Science Still in view

Skills

- HTML
- CSS
- JavaScript
- · Git/Github
- Adobe Photoshop
- MJML (MailJet Markup Language)

Personal Details

• GitHub: github.com/Cosibe